http://www.givainc.com/privacy-policy.cfm

Giva Privacy Policy
Giva respects your privacy. We want to make use of individual identifying information that you provide to us for purposes of serving you better. "Individual identifying information" is information that enables us to identify you, such as your email address, name, title and address. Giva uses the individual identifying information in order to personalize your experience on our Web site and also to be able to selectively send you communications that may be of interest to you, either electronically or otherwise.
Giva websites and products also comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the EU to the United States. Giva has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. For more information on the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, including the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles, and to view the scope of Giva's certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.
EU individuals have rights to access personal data about them, and to limit use and disclosure of their personal data. Giva acknowledges the right of EU individuals to access their personal data pursuant to the Privacy Shield and will grant individuals reasonable access to personal information it received pursuant to these Principles. In addition, Giva will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete such information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete. An individual may request to access his or her information, or otherwise correct, amend, or delete his or her information pursuant to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles by contacting us. With our Privacy Shield certification, Giva has committed to respect those rights.
Also, as part of our participation in these EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, we have agreed to dispute resolution by JAMS for disputes relating to our compliance. If you have any questions or complaints regarding our compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, please contact us. If contacting us does not resolve the issue, you may raise the issue with JAMS here. Please see our full EU-U.S. Privacy Shield notice for more information.
Giva's policy regarding use of your individual identifying information supplied to us or collected via your experience at our online website covers these areas:
1. Notice and Disclosure
This Privacy Policy is made available to you in order to make you aware of how Giva collects and uses individual identifying information of visitors to Giva's Web site.
Giva collects the following information regarding visitors to our Web site: domain name, name, information regarding what pages are accessed, information volunteered by you, such as survey information, email address, or site registrations, and your preferred means of communication.
Giva does not make individual identifying information available to third parties, including business partners, for marketing purposes. Giva does use such information to contact people for marketing purposes.
2. Choice/Consent
When you sign up for an email list, you will be given instructions at that time on how to remove yourself from that list.
Access to certain of Giva's web pages require a login and password. The use of those Web pages, and the information from those sites, are governed by a written agreement between your employer and Giva. Your individual identifying information may be retained by Giva includes, but is not limited to, verifying compliance with the agreement and logging all usage and activity.
3. Data Quality and Access
The accuracy of your individual identifying information is important to Giva. We are working on ways to make it easier for you to review and correct the information that Giva maintains about you.
4. Use of Cookies
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web Sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of the Giva Web Site use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of the site information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.
5. Web Beacons
Giva uses Web beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about customers and visitors' usage of Giva's Web Sites and interaction with emails from Giva. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular Web site tied to the Web beacon, and a description of a Web site tied to the Web beacon. For example, Giva may place Web beacons in marketing emails that notify Giva when you click on a link in the email that directs you to one of Giva's Web Sites. Giva uses Web beacons to operate and improve Giva's Web Sites and email communications.
The Giva Difference
Overview
Products
Customer Service
IT Help Desk
Asset Management
Knowledge Management
IT Change Management
| © 2020 Giva, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
